Guide to the J. Mayone Stycos papers,1955-2004.
Stycos, J. Mayone papers, 1955-2004.
- Series V. Grants and Programs
  - Application for Continuation of Grant for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1986 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Notice of Grant Awarded for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change" Year 1, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change" Year 1, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change" Year 1 revised copy, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Abstract of Research Plan for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", c.a. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change: A Longitudinal Study of Adolescents in a Developing Nation", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Proposal for "Modernization, Modernity and Psycho-Demographic Change: A Longitudinal Study of Adolescents in a Developing Nation, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Summary Proposal Budget for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", Jan. 1, 1983-Dec. 31, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Grant Application for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Grant Application for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Summary Statement of Application Review for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Abstract for "Modernization, Modernity, and Psycho-Demographic Change" (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Ford Foundation, 1970-1988 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Ford Foundation (Mexico), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Ford Foundation-Nigeria (Gwatkin), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Ford Foundation, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Ford Foundation, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Ford Foundation, 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Proposal for "The Diffusion of Fertility Attitudes and Contraception", 1987 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Grant Application and Proposal for "International Population Program", 1987 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Fertility and Fertility Change", 1986 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Final Report on Cornell's International Population Program, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Grant Application for "Training in International Population Research: Fertility, and Population Policy", 1977 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "International Population Program", 1976 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Appointment of Trainee forms, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - "Training in International Population Research", 1974 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Notice of Grant Awarded and Related Correspondence for "Training in International Population Research", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - International Population Program Data Sets 1963-1973, April 1973 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Notice of Grant Award and Related Correspondence for "Training in International Population Research", 1972 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Training Grant Application for "Training in International Population Research", 1972 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Progress Report for Graduate Training Grant for "Training in International Population Research", 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Notice of Grant Awarded and Related Information for "International Population Program", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Academic Approval of Sponsored Project for "International Population Program", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence for Research Training Grant, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Progress Report for Graduate Training Grant for "Training in International Population Research", 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Progress Report for Graduate Training Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Training in International Population Research", 1969 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Expenditure Reports: Training Grants: Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 7/1/68-6/30/69 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - International Population Program, c.a. 1962 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Notice of Grant Award for "Immigrants, Minorities and Their Opportunities: 1940-1950", 1986 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Report on Research Grant for "How Do Immigrants and Ethnic Minorities Sponsor the Education of Their Children", 1985 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Grant Application for "Immigrants, Minorities and Their Opportunities: 1940-1950", 1985 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Grant Application for "Immigrants, Minorities and Their Opportunities: 1940-1950", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence Re: Costa Rica, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Contract Between Cornell University and The National University Foundation of Costa Rica, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence on "Education, Modernization, and Fertility: A Longitudinal Study of Adolescents in a Developing Nation", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Academic Approval for "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence on "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Academic Approval for "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence on "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence on "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Academic Approval for "Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management & Cultural Change", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Proposal Budget for "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1982 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence on "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1982 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Cornell University Correspondence on "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1982 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence on "The Sex Ratio in Ecuador: Cultural Management and Cultural Change", 1982 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Printed Sheets Re: Ecuador (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Informal Project Proposal Outline for Two Films on Greek Culture and Social Problems, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - NICHHD- Year 01, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Series VI. Audio and Films
  - 8mm films of family and travel, F-1587-1590 (Box 32)
    See the empty film boxes within this box for descriptions.
  - Unlabelled audio reel, tr-10821 (Box 32)